It’s time for another meeting!
又要开会了！
If you have a job, the chances are some of your working week will be taken up attending a few of them.
如果你有工作，那么你一周的工作时间中，很可能会有一部分用来参加几次会议。
You and your colleagues will gather together in a meeting room, be talked at for an hour and come out wondering what was the point of it?
你和同事们会聚集在会议室里，听人喋喋不休地讲一个小时，出来后却在想：这会议到底有什么意义？
Of course, it is sometimes necessary to meet to discuss things, share information, voice your opinion and agree a way forward – but are there any other benefits?
当然，有时候开会是必要的——讨论事情、分享信息、表达观点、商定前进方向——但除此之外，还有其他好处吗？
Recent research has suggested that we attend more meetings than ever before – and that's more time listening and talking than actually doing our jobs.
最近的研究表明，我们参加的会议比以往任何时候都多——而且花在听和说上的时间，比实际工作的时间还要多。
Professor Patrik Hall from the University of Malmo told the BBC that this is partly due to more “meetings-intense” roles such as managerial and strategy jobs.
马尔默大学的帕特里克·霍尔教授向英国广播公司表示，部分原因是出现了更多“会议密集型”岗位，比如管理岗和战略岗。
These require more meetings with teams and other stakeholders.
这些岗位需要与团队及其他利益相关者召开更多会议。
But, he says, despite there being more of them, "few decisions are made".
但他说，尽管会议变多了，“却很少做出决策”。
It’s possible that it’s managers on a power trip who set up these meetings – a way of controlling staff, imposing new rules and regulations and asserting their authority.
有可能是那些一心满足权力欲的经理们安排了这些会议——这是他们控制员工、推行新规章制度、彰显权威的一种方式。
But as Professor Hall points out: "Many managers don't know what to do," and when they are "unsure of their role", they respond by generating more meetings.
但正如霍尔教授所指出的：“很多经理不知道该做什么”，当他们“对自己的角色感到不确定时”，就会通过召开更多会议来应对。
And to make matters worse, some meetings involve a pre or post-meeting which eats into even more of the working day.
更糟糕的是，有些会议还会附带会前会或会后会，这进一步占用了工作日的时间。
But the researchers from the University of Malmo have found that a meeting can be seen as a form of ‘therapy’ – it doesn’t have to have an outcome and doesn’t have to be meaningless.
但马尔默大学的研究人员发现，会议可以被视为一种“心理疗愈”——它不一定需要有结果，也不一定是毫无意义的。
So, if you’re just doodling or glancing at your smartphone as your boss drones on, it’s worth considering that a meeting can be an opportunity to demonstrate your talents, express frustration, question ideas and spend time bonding with your colleagues.
所以，当你的老板喋喋不休时，如果你只是在涂鸦或翻看手机，不妨想一想：会议其实可以是一个展示才华、表达不满、质疑想法以及与同事建立感情的机会。
There are a few things to be considered if a meeting is to be a success: it needs an agenda that is adhered to plus an opportunity to discuss any other business, and it should be booked for a short period of time – otherwise the meeting will expand to fit the time that’s been allocated.
要让会议取得成功，有几件事需要考虑：需要有一个严格遵守的议程，加上可以讨论其他事项的机会，而且会议时间应该预约得短一些——否则会议会自动拉长，填满分配给它的时间。
And, as Professor Hall says, the “equality” of participants is important.
此外，正如霍尔教授所说，参会者之间的“平等性”也很重要。
But I think I just prefer the advice of Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla and SpaceX, who urged colleagues to walk out of meetings as soon as it becomes obvious that they are not adding value.
但我更倾向于特斯拉和SpaceX的首席执行官埃隆·马斯克的建议，他敦促同事们，一旦发现会议对自己没有价值，就立即离开。
"It's not rude to leave," he explains. "It's rude to make someone stay and waste their time."
“离开并不无礼，”他解释道，“让别人留下来浪费时间才是无礼的。”
Right, I’m off!
好了，我要走了！